Column description

- originalTitle: 		Original title, in the original language.
- runtimeMinutes: 		Primary runtime of the title, in minutes.
- isAdult: 			Whether or not the title is for adult. 0: non-adult title; 1: adult title.
- startYear: 			Represents the release year of a title. In the case of TV Series, it is the series start year.
- endYear: 			TV Series end year.
- numVotes: 			Number of votes the title has received.
- numRegions: 	 		The regions number for this version of the title.
- worstRating: 			Worst title rating.
- bestRating: 			Best title rating.
- canHaveEpisodes:		Whether or not the title can have episodes.
- isRatable: 			Whether or not the title can be rated by users.
- totalImages:			Total Number of Images for the title within the IMDb title page.
- totalVideos: 			Total Number of Videos for the title within the IMDb title page.
- totalCredits:			Total Number of Credits for the title.
- criticReviewsTotal:		Total Number of Critic Reviews.
- awardWins:			Number of awards the title won.
- awardNominationsExcludeWins: 	Number of award nominations excluding wins.
- titleType:			The type/format of the title (e.g. movie, short, tvseries, tvepisode, video, etc).
- rating:			IMDB title rating class.
- ratingCount: 			The total number of user ratings submitted for the title.
- countryOfOrigin: 		The country where the title was primarily produced.
- genres: 			The genre(s) associated with the title (e.g., drama, comedy, action).
- userReviewsTotal  		Total Number of Users Reviews.



